Feena Fung

🙃 8 Park Rd., Toronto, ON, Canada, M4W 3S5

📞 +1 (437) 263-2220 | 💌 feenafungftl@gmail.com | 🛅 LinkedIn | ⊕ Portfolio | ⊕ GitHub

Summary

Dedicated full-stack developer with 3 years of experience in IT industry with academic background in computing, information systems, data science and statistics. Skills include web development with React, Java & JavaScript programming, SQL, systems analysis and design, cloud computing in AWS & Azure. Easy-going, unflappable, eager to learn and love to take challenges.

Skills

Web Development

- JavaScriptHTML5
- TypeScriptCSS
- ReactSCSS
- Node.js

- Software Development
- Java
- SpringBoot
- Hibernate

Databases

- Oracle DBAWS
- PostgreSQL
- Agile

Miscellaneous

MongoDBGit

Experiences

Analyst Programmer, IBM China/Hong Kong Ltd.

RESTful API

02/2021 - 02/2022

Responsible for developing data warehouse solutions with AWS and ETL (Informatica PowerCenter)

- Engaged in revenue management system data warehouse project for Cathay Pacific Airways Ltd
- Worked agilely with teams in daily morning stand-up and afternoon catch-up meetings
- Gained understanding of business domain knowledge and converted user requirements into an efficient analytics solution for subsequent revenue management and planning
- Developed daily, weekly, and monthly snapshots with **SQL** and **Informatica PowerCenter**
- Supported data ingestion to AWS Redshift with Apache Airflow, AWS S3, AWS DynamoDB

Programmer, DXC Technology Ltd.

05/2020 - 02/2021

Responsible for application development with Java, Spring, JSP, jQuery, Hibernate and Oracle DB

- Engaged in performance assessment scoring system project for Hong Kong Housing Authority
- Developed system functions with CRUD operations and corresponding UI screens
- Prepared test case documentation and automated integration test script with Selenium
- Developed 40+ user reports for performance review with Jasper Report

ICT Graduate Trainee, PCCW Solutions Ltd.

08/2019 - 05/2020

Responsible for web app development with React, TypeScript, LESS, Java, SpringBoot, and Oracle DB

- Engaged in license application review and approval system project for Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission, greatly enhanced application efficiency with e-forms, application tracking and interactive features
- Gave feedbacks on UI design prototype (Figma) and communicated with business analysts
- Worked independently for application dashboard module and produced 60+ user interfaces
- Discussed RESTful API design and feasibility with backend programmers

Sandwich Intern, CLP Power Hong Kong Ltd.

06/2018 - 02/2019

Responsible for supporting enterprise internal systems and digital transformation projects

- Department: Group Information Technology (COE Digital & Enterprise)
- Communicated with stakeholders and converted user requirements, business processes and logic into technical specifications with workflows using MS Visio
- Performed end-to-end testing and prepared test automation scripts for 10+ e-forms on ServiceNow (SaaS)

Qualifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

01/2022

AWS Training and Certification

Designing high-available, cost-efficient, fault-tolerant, and scalable distributed systems on AWS

- Suggest the best practices for building well-architected solutions on AWS
- Take AWS security services and features into consideration

Microsoft Certified Azure Data Fundamental

07/2021

Microsoft Corporation

Knowledge of core data concepts and related Microsoft Azure data services

Microsoft Certified Azure Al Fundamental

06/2021

Microsoft Corporation

Knowledge of machine learning (ML), artificial intelligence (AI) and API concepts and related
 Microsoft Azure services, e.g., Azure Machine Learning, and Azure Bot Service

Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamental

05/2021

Microsoft Corporation

 Knowledge of core Microsoft Azure services, core solutions and management tools, general security and network security, governance, privacy, and compliance features, Microsoft Azure cost management, and service level agreements

Languages

- Fluent in English
 - o IELTS 6.5 (Listening 7.0, Reading 6.5, Writing 6.5, Speaking 6.0)
 - TOEIC (Listening & Reading 920/990, Speaking & Writing 320/400)
- Fluent in Mandarin & Native in Cantonese

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A)

09/2015 - 07/2019

City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

Second Class Honours, Upper Division (CGPA: 3.22/4.3)

- Major: Business Analysis (Management Science)
- Minors: Computing & Information Management for Financial Services
- Courses include Systems Analysis and Design (A), Business Programming with Spreadsheet (A),
 Big Data Analytics (A), Business Intelligence and Analytics (A-), Java Programming (B+)
- Had been to Victoria University of Wellington, New Zealand as Semester Exchange Student
 - Information management courses: Databases (A+), Business Analytics (B+)